<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Judy\'s 30 Days App</string>
    <string name="routine_title_1">Day 1 :Took a long walk in the park and enjoyed the beautiful sunset.</string>
    <string name="routine_description_1">Going to somewhere like a park can calm you and make you enjoy your own\nsolitude. As you take a long walk, the rustling leaves and chirping birds become\nyour companions. The grand finale of this peaceful journey is the beautiful sunset,\na spectacle that paints the sky with hues of orange and pink, leaving you in awe of\nnature\'s beauty.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_2">Day 2:Had a movie night with friends .</string>
    <string name="routine_description_2">Having a movie night with friends is a wonderful way to strengthen bonds and\ncreate lasting memories. It provides an opportunity to share laughter, tears, and\nthoughts, all while enjoying a good film. More than just entertainment, these\ngatherings foster a sense of belonging and camaraderie, making them an\nimportant part of our social lives.\n</string>
    <string name="routine_title_3">Day 3:Spent the day exploring a local museum.\n</string>
    <string name="routine_description_3">Spending the day exploring a local museum is a valuable experience that enriches\nour understanding of culture and history. It allows us to appreciate the artistic and\nhistorical treasures that our locality has to offer. Moreover, it fosters a sense of\ncommunity pride and identity, making it an important activity for both personal\ngrowth and community engagement</string>
    <string name="routine_title_4">Day 4:Go to a local café and enjoy some quiet reading time.</string>
    <string name="routine_description_4">Visiting a local café for some quiet reading time is a delightful way to unwind and\nnourish your mind. It provides a peaceful environment where you can dive into\nthe pages of a book, momentarily escaping from the hustle and bustle of daily life.\nThis practice not only enhances your knowledge but also promotes mental\nrelaxation, making it a significant part of personal growth and self-care.\n</string>
    <string name="routine_title_5">Day 5: Having picnic with my whole family at the beach .</string>
    <string name="routine_description_5">Having a picnic with your whole family at the beach is a beautiful way to foster\nstronger bonds and create cherished memories. It provides a relaxed setting\nwhere everyone can enjoy each other’s company, share stories, and laugh\ntogether. These shared experiences not only bring joy in the moment but also\nstrengthen family ties, making them an essential part of maintaining healthy and\nloving relationships.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_6">Day 6: Going to Baguio for a family vacation .\n</string>
    <string name="routine_description_6">Going to Baguio for a family vacation is a wonderful opportunity to create lasting\nmemories and deepen familial bonds. The cool climate, scenic views, and unique\nexperiences that Baguio offers provide a refreshing break from the usual routine.\nSuch vacations not only offer relaxation and enjoyment but also strengthen family\nrelationships, making them an integral part of nurturing a loving and supportive\nfamily environment</string>
    <string name="routine_title_7">Day 7: Attended on a worship ceremony with our Pastor .\n</string>
    <string name="routine_description_7">Attending a worship ceremony with your pastora is a meaningful way to nurture\nyour spiritual growth and strengthen your faith. It provides a space for reflection,\nprayer, and connection with a community that shares your beliefs. These\ngatherings not only offer spiritual guidance but also foster a sense of belonging\nand unity, making them a vital part of your spiritual journey.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_8">Day 8: Making a homemade graham balls for dessert.\n</string>
    <string name="routine_description_8">Making homemade graham balls for dessert is a delightful way to express\ncreativity and enjoy the process of cooking. It allows you to explore different\nflavors and textures, resulting in a unique dessert that caters to your taste. This\nactivity not only provides a delicious treat but also enhances your culinary skills,\nmaking it a fun and rewarding experience.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_9">Day 9: Watching a Koreanovela.</string>
    <string name="routine_description_9">Watching a Koreanovela can be a delightful and enriching experience. It not only\nprovides entertainment but also offers a glimpse into Korean culture, traditions,\nand language, broadening our understanding of the world. Moreover, the intricate\nstorylines and well-developed characters can stimulate our emotions and\nthoughts, enhancing our empathy and critical thinking skills</string>
    <string name="routine_title_10">Day 10. Hiking with friends.\n</string>
    <string name="routine_description_10">Hiking with friends is a wonderful way to connect with nature while strengthening\nyour relationships. It offers a unique opportunity to work together, overcome\nchallenges, and share memorable experiences, fostering a sense of camaraderie\nand mutual support. Additionally, it promotes physical health and mental wellbeing, as the exercise and fresh air can reduce stress and increase happiness.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_11">"Day 11: Joining in a Zumba event in our community "</string>
    <string name="routine_description_11">Joining a Zumba event in our community is not just a fun-filled activity, but it also\nholds significant importance. It serves as a platform for us to engage with our\nneighbors, fostering a sense of unity and camaraderie, while also promoting a\nhealthy lifestyle through dance and exercise. Moreover, it’s a wonderful\nopportunity to break away from our daily routines, allowing us to enjoy, express\nourselves, and create memorable experiences together.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_12">Day 12: Making a DIY design for my room</string>
    <string name="routine_description_12">Making a DIY design for your room is a meaningful and creative endeavor. It allows\nyou to express your personal style and preferences, making your space truly feel\nlike your own. Moreover, it encourages resourcefulness and creativity, as you find\nways to repurpose items or create something new from scratch. Ultimately, this\nprocess not only results in a more personalized room, but also provides a sense of\naccomplishment and pride in your own work.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_13">Day 13: Painted a landscape inspired by a dream.</string>
    <string name="routine_description_13">Painting a landscape inspired by a dream is a profound and imaginative journey. It\nallows you to translate your subconscious thoughts and feelings into a tangible\nform, providing a unique insight into your inner world. This creative process not\nonly enhances your artistic skills but also serves as a therapeutic outlet, helping\nyou understand and express your emotions better. Ultimately, it’s a beautiful\nblend of dream exploration and artistic expression, making it a truly enriching\nexperience.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_14">Day 14. Spent the day in a family reunion</string>
    <string name="routine_description_14">Spending the day at a family reunion is a precious opportunity to strengthen\nfamilial bonds and create lasting memories. It allows everyone to catch up, share\nstories, and celebrate the unique history and traditions</string>
    <string name="routine_title_15">Day 15 : Going to a local markets with my friends.</string>
    <string name="routine_description_15">Going to a local market with friends is a delightful and meaningful activity. It’s a\nchance to support local businesses and discover unique items or foods that you\nmight not find elsewhere. Moreover, it’s a social experience that allows you to\nbond with your friends, share discoveries, and create memorable experiences, all\nwhile contributing to your local economy.\n</string>
    <string name="routine_title_16">Day 16: Spending the day in a Movie Theater</string>
    <string name="routine_description_16">Spending the day in a movie theater is a wonderful way to immerse yourself in\ndifferent stories and worlds. It provides an escape from daily routines and\nstresses, allowing you to relax and enjoy the magic of cinema. Moreover, sharing\nthis experience with others can spark interesting discussions and deepen your\nrelationships, making it a valuable social activity as well.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_17">Day 17 : Making a homemade carbonara</string>
    <string name="routine_description_17">Making homemade carbonara is a delightful and enriching experience. It not only\nallows you to explore your culinary skills but also gives you the freedom to\ncustomize the dish to your liking, enhancing your appreciation for food and\ncooking. Moreover, it’s a wonderful way to share a piece of your creativity with\nothers, turning a simple meal into a meaningful and enjoyable moment.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_18">Day 18 : Attend a live music concert .</string>
    <string name="routine_description_18">Attending a live music concert is an exhilarating experience that can uplift your\nspirits and create lasting memories. It allows you to connect with the music on a\ndeeper level, as you witness the passion and talent of the artists firsthand.\nMoreover, sharing this experience with others, whether they’re friends or fellow\nfans, can foster a sense of community and shared joy, making it a truly enriching\nsocial event.\n</string>
    <string name="routine_title_19">Day 19 : Attending a yoga event .</string>
    <string name="routine_description_19">Attending a yoga event is a fantastic way to promote both physical and mental\nhealth. It provides an opportunity to learn new yoga techniques, deepen your\nunderstanding of the practice, and connect with your inner self in a peaceful and\nsupportive environment. Additionally, it fosters a sense of community as you\nshare this wellness journey with others, making it a holistic and enriching\nexperience.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_20">Day 20: Spent the day in visiting our relatives in city .</string>
    <string name="routine_description_20">Spending the day visiting relatives in the city is a meaningful way to nurture family\nbonds. It provides an opportunity to catch up, share stories, and create new\nmemories, strengthening the ties that bind your family together. Moreover, it’s a\nreminder of the importance of family in our lives, providing a sense of belonging\nand continuity amidst the fast-paced rhythm of city life</string>
    <string name="routine_title_21">Day 21 : Attending a cooking class .\n</string>
    <string name="routine_description_21">Attending a cooking class is a fantastic way to expand your culinary skills and\nknowledge. It provides hands-on experience and professional guidance, helping\nyou to master new techniques and recipes. Moreover, it’s a social activity that\nallows you to connect with fellow food enthusiasts, making it not just an\neducational experience, but a fun and enriching one as well.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_22">Day 22: Jogging with my sisters.</string>
    <string name="routine_description_22">Jogging with your sisters is a wonderful way to combine fitness and family time. It\npromotes physical health, helping you all to stay active and fit, while also\nproviding a regular opportunity to catch up and strengthen your bond. Moreover,\nit fosters a sense of mutual support and motivation, as you encourage each other\nto reach your fitness goals, making it a beneficial and enjoyable routine.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_23">Day 23 : Going to a dance practice for the school project .</string>
    <string name="routine_description_23">Going to a dance practice for a school project is a valuable experience that\nenhances your artistic skills and teamwork. It allows you to express yourself\nthrough movement, improving your physical coordination and rhythm. Moreover,\nworking together with your classmates towards a common goal fosters a sense of\ncamaraderie and cooperation, making it not just a dance practice, but a lesson in\ncollaboration and dedication as well.\n</string>
    <string name="routine_title_24">Day 24: Spent the day in a beach with my family .\n</string>
    <string name="routine_description_24">Spending the day at the beach with family is a wonderful way to create lasting\nmemories and strengthen your bonds. It provides a relaxing environment to enjoy\neach other’s company, share stories, and have fun, whether it’s building\nsandcastles or playing in the waves. Moreover, it’s a reminder of the simple joys in\nlife, like the warmth of the sun and the laughter of loved ones, making it a truly\nenriching experience.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_25">Day 25 : Group study with friends .\n</string>
    <string name="routine_description_25">Having a group study with friends is a beneficial activity that enhances your\nlearning experience. It allows for the exchange of ideas and perspectives, helping\nyou to understand complex concepts and solve problems more effectively.\nMoreover, it fosters a sense of camaraderie and mutual support, making studying\nnot just a solitary task, but a collaborative and enjoyable process.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_26">Day 26 : Spent the day in biking activity .</string>
    <string name="routine_description_26">Spending the day in a biking activity is a fantastic way to combine exercise with\nenjoyment. It promotes physical fitness, improving your cardiovascular health and\nmuscle strength, while also allowing you to explore your surroundings in a fun and\neco-friendly way. Moreover, it provides a sense of freedom and adventure, making\nit not just a physical activity, but a mentally refreshing one as well.\n</string>
    <string name="routine_title_27">Day 27: Making a art project .\n</string>
    <string name="routine_description_27">Creating an art project is a beautiful way to express your creativity and\nindividuality. It allows you to explore different mediums and techniques,\nenhancing your artistic skills and broadening your understanding of art. Moreover,\nthe process of creating can be therapeutic and fulfilling, providing a sense of\naccomplishment and a unique outlet for self-expression.</string>
    <string name="routine_title_28">Day 28 : Going to a newly open restaurant .</string>
    <string name="routine_description_28">Going to a newly opened restaurant is an exciting adventure that stimulates your\nsenses and expands your culinary horizons. It allows you to discover new flavors\nand dishes, enhancing your appreciation for different cuisines</string>
    <string name="routine_title_29">Day 29 : Going to a tulip flower shop .</string>
    <string name="routine_description_29">Visiting a tulip flower shop is a delightful experience that can brighten your day\nand bring joy to others. It allows you to appreciate the beauty and variety of\ntulips, enhancing your understanding and love for these charming blooms.\nMoreover, whether you’re buying for yourself or as a gift, the act of choosing and\ngiving flowers can spread positivity and express care, making it a simple yet\nmeaningful activity.\n</string>
    <string name="routine_title_30">Day 30 : Spending the whole day in my favorite place where I experience peace\nand healing .</string>
    <string name="routine_description_30">Spending the whole day in your favorite place, where you experience peace and\nhealing, is a deeply nourishing practice. It provides a sanctuary for you to unwind,\nreflect, and reconnect with yourself, promoting mental and emotional well-being\n</string>
</resources>